

CONTACT



Email

ishanmwaduge@gmail.com



Phone

+94 76 7711 597 +94 70 2012 900



Location

Basswaththa, Mahawella Road, Gonapinuwala, Galle, Sri Lanka



Website

imwaduge.me

SOCIAL MEDIA



LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/imwaduge



Behance

behance.net/imwaduge



Github

github.com/imwaduge

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Logo & Brand Identity Design

UI-UX Design | Prototyping

Web Development

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React JS

PHP | MySQL | JAVA | C#

Digital Marketing

SOFT SKILLS

Creative thinking Team work Problem-solving Multi-tasking

ISHAN MADUSANKA WADUGE

UI/UX DESIGNER | BRAND DESIGNER | UNDERGRADUATE

ABOUT

I am a freelance designer with five years of experience. I have completed more than 250 projects for international clients since 2018. To Expand my knowledge, I am pursuing a Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology (Honours) specializing in multimedia technology at the University of Sri Jayawardenepura. I am passionate about using my skills to help organizations overcome challenges and succeed long-term. I am currently looking for career opportunities that will allow me to work together with teams and clients to create user - friendly solutions for the digital world. I enjoy working in an environment that offers growth and learning opportunities.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology Honours

2020 - Present

Faculty of Technology, University of Sri Jayewardenepura

(Undergraduate - BICT Hons)

G.C.E Advanced Level Examination - Technology Stream

2016 - 2018



St' Anthony's College

Information and Communication Technology - A Engineering Technology - B Science For Technology - B

Z Score - 2.16

District Rank - 11

G.C.E Ordinary Level Examination

2005 - 2015



📵 G/Saralankara Maha Vidyalaya

Information and Communication Technology - A

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Services

2023 - Present



X Fixelit

UI/UX design, Logo & Brand identity design, Packaging design, Website and Web application development, Video production.

UI/UX Designer

2022 - 2023



UI/UX design, Front-end development, Logo & Brand identity design, Logo animation.

Brand Designer

2019 - Present



As an experienced graphic designer with 5 years of industry expertise, I have honed my skills in Brand identity design and UI/UX design. I have successfully completed over 250 projects.

PROJECTS

HireNow - Service Selling Platform (Group)

UI-UX Design and developed web-based "HireNow" Service Selling Platform on Figma, HTML, CSS, JS, React.

Automated Plant Watering System (Group)

Design Plant watering system arduino base and developed Mobile Application.

GPSI Premium - Car Service Center

Designed and developed a website for a car service center.

Ocean Epic - Game designed and developed (Windows, Android)

J'pura FOSS - UI/UX Design (2023)

I designed the user interface and user experience for the J'pura FOSS Community website.

Plot Details CRUD System - DIVISIONAL SECRETARIAT

I designed and developed a CRUD system for the Divisional Secretariat, creating wireframes, designing the user interface, coding the system, and testing functionality.

Online Type Racing Game - UI/UX Design

CERTIFICATION

English Diploma in British Way English Academy

Graphic Design Course in Future World IPS

Computer Hardware Engineering Course in Nanasa Education Institute

Digital Marketing Course in Google Digital Garage

Front End Development - HTML, CSS Courses in Great Learning Academy

UI / UX Course in Great Learning Academy

Introduction to Design Thinking Course in Great Learning Academy

Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2023 Course in Udemy

JavaScript | Ultimate Guide Course in Udemy

React Js Courses in Udemy (Ongoing)

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Participated in UI/UX Challenge - Design Code 2022

Participated in several gaming competition

Graphic designer at the J'PURA FOSS Community

Member of the J'PURA Flames

Passed the Dhamma School Final Certificate Examination

Senior Prefect in 2014, 2015

DECLARATION

I certify that the above details and informations are true and accurate to the best of my knowledge.

20.05.2023

Date



SOFTWARE SKILLS

Figma | Adobe XD

Adobe Illustrator | Photoshop

Premiere Pro | After Effects

Microsoft Office Package

TEST SCORES

Adobe Illustrator Test - Fiverr

2021 Score: 8/10 (TOP 10%)

Adobe Photoshop Test - Fiverr

2021 Score: 9.5/10 (TOP 10%)

INTERESTS

UI/UX Design

Front End Development

Logo Design

Brand Identity Design

Digital Marketing

PERSONAL PROFILE

BIRTHDAY - 22.06.1999

GENDER - Male

NATIONALITY - Sri Lankan

MARITAL STATUS - Single

NIC - 991746927v

LANGUAGES - Sinhala, English

NON-RELATED REFEREES

Dr. Pulasthi Gunawardhana

Senior Lecturer

Department of Information Communication Technology, Faculty o Technology, University of Sri Jayewardenepura.

Email: pulasthi@sjp.ac.lk Mobile: +94 77 488 6388

Chamila Karunatilake

Lecturer

Department of Information Communication Technology, Faculty of Technology, University of Sri Jayewardenepura.

Email : chamilakarunatilake@sjp.ac.lk

Mobile: +94 76 460 8026